

Profile

Open-minded and passionate undergraduate with close to 2 years of learning and experience in the IT field, bringing forth valuable industry experience and a passion for management. Adept in analytical thinking, strategic planning, leadership, and building strong relationships with people around me. Highly interested in learning about how IT applies in diverse fields and hope to contribute well to the company while simultaneously improving myself.

Employment History

Finance Analyst Internship at Singapore Engraving & Offset Plate Making, Singapore

February 2021 — July 2022

- Managed inventory of goods being taken in and out from the company
- Helped to increase customer return rates by providing excellent customer service at all times.

Server at Staffie, Singapore

February 2020 — Present

- Worked well independently as well as collaboratively.
- Handled food with sanitation and safety in mind.
- Worked to achieve high customer satisfaction rates by providing optimal customer service
- Worked to ensure a neat and attractive environment for customers.
- Settled any customer disputes in a professional and pleasant manner.

Education

Diploma in Big Data & Analyst, Temasek Polytechnic, SingaporeApril 2021 — Present

Technical Diploma of Mechanical Engineering, Institute of Technical Education East, Singapore

April 2019 — April 2021

■ References

Ms KellyfromSingapore Engraving & Offset Plate Making (+65) 97803461

Details

Blk 271, Pasir Ris Street 21 Singapore, 510271 Singapore (+65) 85715963 benjamin.seng.wx@gmail.com

Date of birth

2 March 2002

Nationality

Singaporean

Links

LinkedIn Profile Gmail

Skills

Java

Tableau

Microsoft Excel

SQL

Python

Leadership Skills

Microsoft Power BI

Machine Learning

Hobbies

I love to get active doing my favorite sports like volleyball, competitive Rock Climbing when I'm away from the computer.

Languages

English

Chinese